{
    "id": "c545d5ee9f9647d5af0af7aac4e4e8f4",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A general pardon of political offenders is …………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "generosity",
                "leniency",
                "clemency",
                "amnesty"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the term ‘meet one’s Waterloo’ mean?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "die an ignoble death",
                "fight with a formidable opponent",
                "meet one’s final defeat"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting …………………… . with a vote of thanks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ended",
                "stopped",
                "concluded"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You must ………………….. your expenditure if you don’t want to fall into the debt trap.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cut down",
                "cut up",
                "cut off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A person who rules without consulting the opinion of others is a/an………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "democrat",
                "aristocrat",
                "autocrat"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Find the synonym of the word Ubiquitous",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Everywhere",
                "Nowhere",
                "Somewhere"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Select the word which can be used both as an adjective and a verb.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "obey",
                "lame",
                "long"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not late, ………………… ..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "amn't I",
                "aren't I",
                "is I"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has …………………….. the picture on the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hang",
                "hanged",
                "hung"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following term is used to refer to the act of killing one’s own brother?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "regicide",
                "fratricide",
                "genocide"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The engagement was called ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "All the characters in this movie are ‘fictitious’. Choose the term which is closest in meaning to ‘fictitious’.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "original",
                "famous",
                "infamous",
                "imaginary"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        }
    ]
}